Madeira
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Madiera
2.1.1.1.14
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1197
- Madiera, 2.1.1.1.14
  - Child at fort, 1909; 40; 23010; 4x5 (Box 1197)
  - Old fort, Signal Station, 1909; 41; 23011; 4x5 (Box 1197)
  - S.S. Coronia from old fort, Signal Station, 1909; 42; 23024; 27; 5x7 (Box 1197)
  - S.S. Coronia and old fort, Signal Station, 1909; 43; 23040; 5x7 (Box 1197)
  - Harbor and Madeira from Signal Station, 1909; 44; 23041; 5x7 (Box 1197)
  - Carro and hedge at Bignonia, 1909; 45; 23027; 5x7 (Box 1197)
  - Trees leading from wharf to Funchal Avenue of Oriental Plane, 1909b; 46; 23030; 12; 5x7 (Box 1197)
  - Men with pigs, Funchal, 1909; 47; 23005; 4x5 (Box 1197)
  - Man with pig, Funchal, 1909; 48; 23006; 4x5 (Box 1197)
  - Group of people in toboggan, 1909; 49; 23007; 4x5 (Box 1197)
  - People carrying toboggan up hill, 1909; 50; 23008; 24; 4x5 (Box 1197)
  - Broken ship in harbor, 1909; 51; 23009; 4x5 (Box 1197)
  Box 1198
- Madiera, 2.1.1.1.14
  - Garden in Funchel with Bougainvillea, 1909; 1; 23023; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - Mrs. Jessie W. Roberson in hammock, Funchal, 1909; 2; 23026; 10; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - Ferns and calla lilies in woods, Funchal, 1909; 3; 23028; 7; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - Bougainvillea on embankment, 1909; 4; 23029; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - Narrow street, Funchal, 1909; 5; 23031; 19; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - Carro by the bignonia vine, Funchal, 1909; 6; 23033; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - Top of funicular railroad, 1909; 7; 23035; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - Carro under big tree, Funchal, 1909; 8; 23036; 2; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - Life on the beach, 1909; 9; 23037; 13; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - Street scene, Funchal, 1909; 10; 23038; 20; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - City and harbor from Signal Station, Funchal, 1909; 11; 23042; 25; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - Frank R. Roberson and Mrs. Jessie W. Roberson and party drinking on toboggan, Funchal, 1909; 12; 23045; 11; 5x7 (Box 1198)